Preliminary Guide to the John S. Bradway Papers, 1922-1949
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List, 51 Boxes
  - N.C. Bar Association, 1934-1935
  - N.C. Commission on Interracial Cooperation, 1934
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1935
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service-Committee on Crime and Law Enforcement, 1934-1935
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service-Resolutions Committee, 1935
  - Memos to/from Dean Horack, 1934-1935
  - Juvenile Court (Durham), 1934-1935
  - Juvenile Court Commission, 1934
  - N.C. Bar Association-Legal Aid Committee, 1934-1935
  - Mental Hygiene Society of Durham-Orange County, 1936
  - Miscellaneous, 1934-1936
  - N.C. Bar Association, 1936-1937
  - N.C. Mental Hygiene Society, 1936-1937
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1936
  - N.C. Probation Commission, 1937
  - N.Y.A., 1936-1937
  - Parliamentary Law, 1936-1937
  - Rotary Club, 1936-1937
  - Roundtable on Legal Aid Clinics, 1936-1937 (Box 34)
  - South Carolina Bar, 1936-1937
  - Traveler's Aid, 1936-1937
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1936
  - State Legislative Council, 1948-1949
  - Symposium Proceedings-"Undergraduate Preparation for Study of Law", 1949. By the Committee on Pre-Legal Education of the Law Faculty of Duke University
  - Durham Community and War Fund, 1945
  - Drafts
  - Examinations, 1945
  - Family Law Seminar Course, 1946 (FERPA rules apply)
  - Family Law Course, 1943-1945 (FERPA rules apply)
  - Family Law Seminar, 1933 (FERPA rules apply)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Act-Student Fund, 1934
  - Federal Emergency Relief Act, 1934-1935
  - N.C. Bar Association, 1933-1934
  - Miscellaneous, 1934-1935
  - Community Chest (Durham), 1934-1935
  - Durham Council of Social Agencies, 1934-1935
  - Examinations, 1934-1935 (FERPA rules apply)
  - Duke Bar Association, 1933
  - Curriculum Committee, 1933
  - Durham Council of Social Agencies, 1934-1935
  - Examinations, 1934-1935 (FERPA rules apply)
  - N.C. Courthouses-Pictures-History
  - Justices of the N.C. Supreme Court
  - Community Relief Committee of Durham and Durham County, 1933-1935
  - Durham Crime Study Club, 1933-1935
  - Citizens' Council, 1933-1934
  - Clinic Staff, 1933-1934
  - Community Chest, 1934
  - Addresses (Speeches), 1932-1935
  - American Association of Social Workers-N.C. Chapter, 1934-1935 (Box 34)
  - Addresses (Speeches), 1933-1934
  - Articles, 1933
  - Bradway-Personal, 1934-1935
  - Budget-Duke Legal Aid Clinic, 1934-1935
  - Budget-Duke Legal Aid Clinic, 1933-1934
  - Biographical Material on N.C. Chief Justices
  - Social Service Directory (Durham), 1934
  - Social Service Index, 1934-1935
  - Transient Bureau, 1934-1935
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1945
  - United War Fund of N.C.
  - W-General Correspondence, 1945
  - Robert Waters' Material, 1945
  - N.C. State Bar, 1945
  - N.C. Probation Commission, 1945
  - N.C. Mental Hygiene Society, 1945
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1945
  - N.C. Bar Association-Committee on War Work, 1945
  - N.C. Mental Hygiene Society, 1947
  - N.C. League for Crippled Children, 1947
  - Nurses, Lectures to, 1947
  - O-General Correspondence, 1947
  - P-General Correspondence, 1947
  - North Carolina-General, 1932
  - Sterilization Law, 1933
  - Community Welfare Committee (Durham and Durham County), 1933-1934
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1947
  - N.C. Probation Commission, 1947
  - Domestic Relations Commission (N.C.), 1947
  - State Legislative Commission (N.C.), 1947
  - Ethics Course, 1947
  - Family Law Course, 1947
  - Family Law Seminar Course, Spring 1947
  - G to L-General Correspondence, 1945 (Box 35)
  - Lawyers for whom Briefs Prepared, 1936-1940
  - Loan Shark Material (N.C.), 1944-1945
  - N.C. Bar Association-Committee on War Work, 1944-1947
  - Proposal for New Pattern in Law School Curriculum, 1946
  - Teaching Materials, undated
  - Classroom Material, 1947
  - Clinic Exam Material, Spring 1947
  - Clinic II-Miscellaneous (FERPA rules apply)
  - Suggested Additions for Clinic Course, 1947
  - Correctional Course, 1947
  - Community Fund (Durham), 1947
  - Columbia, S.C. Meeting of the Southeastern Conference of Law Teachers, 1947
  - Clinical Preparation for Law Practice
  - Miss Mary Grayson Allen
  - Aptitude Tests, 1945
  - Index to Briefs
  - Lt. Thomas D. Bolles
  - Bench and Bar, 1940-1945
  - Bench and Bar, 1938-1940
  - Camp Butner, 1945
  - Memorandum of Law, Spring 1946
  - Durham Child Guidance Clinic, 1947
  - Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1947
  - Durham Chamber of Commerce-Special Committee, 1947
  - Bradley, S.B.-Materials
  - Bench and Bar, 1947
  - Baloptican Material, 1946-1947
  - Memoranda of Law, Fall 1946
  - N.C. Banker's Association, 1943-1944
  - Memoranda of Law, 1945
  - Commission to Study Laws of State relating to Domestic Relations, 1945
  - Carroll material, 1946
  - NALAO material, 1929-1935 (Box 36-50)
  - Personal Correspondence and Financial Material, 1934-1935
  - NALAO material, 1923-1937
  - Chapter Files, The Work of Legal Aid Organizations
  - Articles by Bradway, 1948-1949
  - NALAO material, 1935-1936
  - Personal Material, 1935-1936
  - NALAO material, 1934-1937
  - NALAO travel diaries, 1926-1928; 1931-1934
  - NALAO financial material
  - Secretary's Report to Executive Committee (NALAO)
  - Legislative matters
  - Minimum Statistics, 1934
  - Questionnaire on Installment Purchases
  - Articles by Bradway
  - Subject Files/Correspondence with NALAO member organizations throughout the U.S.
  - Subject Files/Correspondence with NALAO member organizations throughout the U.S.
  - Project on a Convention to establish an International Legal Aid Organization
  - Drafts of Domestic Relations Article
  - American Bar Association
  - National Social Work Council
  - Subject Files/Correspondence with NALAO member organizations
  - Executive Committee (NALAO)
  - Minimum Statistics
  - Minimum Statistics
  - Form Letters
  - Legal Aid Progress
  - NALAO Committees
  - Executive Committee (NALAO)
  - State Survey Reports
  - 1939 NALAO Conference
  - [Contents belong between boxes 8 and 9] Red Vol. 25, 1923-1931 (Box 51 (location unknown))
    Legal Aid Bureau of the Detroit Bar Association
  - Red Vol. 26, 1923-1931
    General Correspondence while at Univ. of Southern California
    Montreal Legal Aid Bureau
    Correspondence with Justin Miller
    Paper: "Plan for Legal Aid Clinic Association"
    Establishment of Legal Aid Society in Birmingham, Ala.
  - Red Vol. 29, 1923-1930
    Outline for A Statistical and Case Study in the Administration of Criminal Justice
    Correspondence, New Orleans, Louisville, Atlanta
    Papers: "Legal Aid Work and Law Schools"; "Legal Aid and Anti-Loan Shark Recorder"